knowledgesutra.com 2011-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Discuss Anything

###  [#1](http://www.knowledgesutra.com/forums/topic/5770-privacy-policy/page__view__findpost__p__40138 "Link to post #1")  

Posted 07 January 2005 - 02:17 AM

Due to the nature of our service, for security reasons, KnowledgeSutra. does collect personally identifiable information about individuals.

Personally identifiable information on individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to either affiliated, or unaffiliated third parties except when such individuals specifically provide such instruction on a voluntary basis at the time of collection. Further, KnowledgeSutra reserves the right to contact a user by email, regarding matters relevant to the underlying service and/or information collected. KnowledgeSutra will never contact users directly through a physical address or by phone, and such information is securely stored after being reviewed.

Users should be aware that KnowledgeSutra is lawfully required to provide personally identifiable information to law authorities, such as the Internet Police as requested, if a criminal offence whether related or non-related to KnowledgeSutra and/or its community has been committed. Additionally upon breach of KnowledgeSutra's Terms Of Service, KnowledgeSutra is required to contact and report the offence to all parties involved in the violation, including but not limited to the violator's Internet Service Provider and Internet Police.

Users also should be aware that non personal information and data may automatically be collected through the standard operation of KnowledgeSutra internet servers or through the use of "cookies." Information about "Cookies" is usually available in the help section of most browsers.

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending an email message stating you do not want to receive e-mail from our company. Users should be aware that it may lead to termination of their specific services associated with KnowledgeSutra and it may be impossible to delete all references to a user without some residual information remaining because of backups and deleted records. We asure you, however, that such residual information - if any - remains secure and covered by this private policy.

KnowledgeSutra reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existance of a new privacy statement.

The policies described herein are effective as of the year 2005. 

0 

##  1 User(s) are reading this topic  
0 members, 1 guests, 0 anonymous users
  *[07 January 2005 - 02:17 AM]: 2005-01-07T02:17:23+00:00
